<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>organisational culture on Ben Fielding - Apprenticeship Portfolio</title>
    <link>/categories/organisational-culture/</link>
    <description>Recent content in organisational culture on Ben Fielding - Apprenticeship Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 15:55:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/organisational-culture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>hack-hw43</title>
      <link>/posts/hack-hw43/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 15:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hack-hw43/</guid>
      <description>Situation VPC flow logs are retained for 30 days in both prod and nonprod environments. Following an audit of logs a ticket was raised to investigate what our log retention periods should be and to make the required changes to our infrastructure.
Task The scope of the ticket was to contact Secure Design Services to find out what log retention periods should be set at and then make the required changes to our core-infra stack to implement this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hack-hw98</title>
      <link>/posts/hack-hw98/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 14:00:48 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hack-hw98/</guid>
      <description>Situation A developer team working the Find and Refer service are alerted within a Slack channel when a file is added to some specific targeted AWS s3 buckets. They have made a request which has been added to the HACK team sprint as a working ticket. They have requested that &amp;lsquo;to support incident management and ease repetitive cognitive load&amp;rsquo; they would also like to be alerted when specific files have NOT been added to their buckets by a given time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 0</title>
      <link>/posts/release0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 10:26:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/release0/</guid>
      <description>Introduction About Me I am Ben Fielding and I work at Department for Work and Pensions, within the Digital Group, as an Apprentice DevOps engineer. My background is mainly in the private sector working within the parking industry. Some of my experience with technology was gained through configuring and repairing parking equipment. Prior to being made redundant in January 2020 I was department lead on a project to build and launch a parking app, which gave me some experience of writing tests, testing, doing user research and working in sprints.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 0</title>
      <link>/posts/release0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 10:26:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/release0/</guid>
      <description>Introduction About Me I am Ben Fielding and I work at Department for Work and Pensions, within the Digital Group, as an Apprentice DevOps engineer. My background is mainly in the private sector working within the parking industry. Some of my experience with technology was gained through configuring and repairing parking equipment. Prior to being made redundant in January 2020 I was department lead on a project to build and launch a parking app, which gave me some experience of writing tests, testing, doing user research and working in sprints.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
