<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>continuous learning and development on Ben Fielding - Apprenticeship Portfolio</title>
    <link>/categories/continuous-learning-and-development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in continuous learning and development on Ben Fielding - Apprenticeship Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 10:26:56 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/continuous-learning-and-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Release 0</title>
      <link>/posts/release0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 10:26:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/release0/</guid>
      <description>Introduction About Me I am Ben Fielding and I work at Department for Work and Pensions, within the Digital Group, as an Apprentice DevOps engineer. My background is mainly in the private sector working within the parking industry. Some of my experience with technology was gained through configuring and repairing parking equipment. Prior to being made redundant in January 2020 I was department lead on a project to build and launch a parking app, which gave me some experience of writing tests, testing, doing user research and working in sprints.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self Led Learning</title>
      <link>/posts/self-led-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 13:43:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/self-led-learning/</guid>
      <description>Team specific courses undertaken during my apprenticeship
  Course title Provider Link to course content Time spent completing Tools and Technologies covered     Setting Up Lambda Functions with S3 Event Triggers Cloud Guru Examples of course content 1 Hour AWS IAM, SNS, Lambda, s3api   Hashicorp Certified: Terraform Associate Pluralsight Examples of course content 8 hours Hashicorp Terraform Certification Path   Technical Writing Courses Google https://developers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
