<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>problem solving on Ben Fielding - Apprenticeship Portfolio</title>
    <link>/categories/problem-solving/</link>
    <description>Recent content in problem solving on Ben Fielding - Apprenticeship Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 17:14:42 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/problem-solving/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AMI Refresh Project</title>
      <link>/posts/ami-refresh-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 17:14:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ami-refresh-project/</guid>
      <description>Situation In order to patch vulnerabilities and install software version updates so as to decrease the attack surface of servers ensuring they are equipped to support feature team applications, a process is in place within our department that builds a new Amazon Machine Image. This is then updated within the application and infrastructure stacks by applying Terraform before finally Auto Scaling Group refreshes are manually carried out to apply the new launch templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack 4235</title>
      <link>/posts/hack-4235/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 18:12:03 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hack-4235/</guid>
      <description>Situation Configuration of Jenkins controller and agents is done by means of a Jenkins module which holds all of the Jenkins configuration in a mixture of xml and other files.
Task In order to standardize the configuration, consul templates should be used to configure the application within the terraform-aws-jenkins module.
Action I decided to use the Plan-Do-Check-Act problem solving technique in my workflow for this ticket as I felt it would be most appropriate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hack-hw98</title>
      <link>/posts/hack-hw98/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 14:00:48 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hack-hw98/</guid>
      <description>Situation A developer team working the Find and Refer service are alerted within a Slack channel when a file is added to some specific targeted AWS s3 buckets. They have made a request which has been added to the HACK team sprint as a working ticket. They have requested that &amp;rsquo;to support incident management and ease repetitive cognitive load&amp;rsquo; they would also like to be alerted when specific files have NOT been added to their buckets by a given time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
